[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the movie The Godfather?", "correct_answer": "Francis Ford Coppola", "incorrect_answers": ["Al Pacino", "Vito Corleone", "Steven Spielberg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the teacher of Plato?", "correct_answer": "Socrates", "incorrect_answers": ["Thales", "Aristotle", "Archimedes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rudolph Walter Wanderone Jr. was a famous player in what sport?", "correct_answer": "pool", "incorrect_answers": ["thoroughbred racing", "professional wrestling", "football"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the real name of the dog who first played the fictitious dog Benji in the series of Benji films?", "correct_answer": "Higgins", "incorrect_answers": ["Benji", "Arnold", "Lassie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The capital city of this country was once known as The Little Paris of Eastern Europe.", "correct_answer": "Romania", "incorrect_answers": ["Bulgaria", "Latvia", "Croatia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is the Pink Cadillac the trademark of Mary Kay beauty products?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The zygomatic processes form the cheek bones.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Painted gold by Auric Goldfinger, the eponymous villain of the film Goldfinger, this female character\u2019s death convinces her sister to take sides with 007.", "correct_answer": "Jill Masterson", "incorrect_answers": ["Tracy Draco", "Rosie Carver", "Melina Havelock"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Due to the presence of a specific protein in the blood plasma octopuses have this unusual blood color.", "correct_answer": "Blue", "incorrect_answers": ["Black", "Bright green", "Fluorescent pink"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Besides screaming, what were villain Skanks last words in The Crow?", "correct_answer": "Skanks dead!", "incorrect_answers": ["Fire it up!", "Abash the devil stood, and felt how awful goodness is.", "Ill kill you!!!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement is true about Mrs. P.F.E. Albee?", "correct_answer": "She was the first Avon lady.", "incorrect_answers": ["She was the first Mary Kay salesperson.", "She was the first woman to practice law in the USA.", "She was the first woman to legally vote in a US Presidential election."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What American star portrayed the character of Viktor Komarovsky in the 1965 drama-romance-war film Doctor Zhivago?", "correct_answer": "Rod Steiger", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Nicholson", "Robert Redford", "Omar Sharif"]}]